Funeral music
He sighs.
- It's here.
Bring me back his egg.
Tension music
Epic music
Cris
Don't worry,
I will protect you.
Soft music
There's a knock.
- Hello.
- Hi, my angel. How are you?
Was it good with Dad?
- Look at,
I won him a plush toy.
and he made us
Beautiful drawings. Look.
- Ah yes, that's...
Wow!
OK, you draw
Getting better and better, that's...
Pretty, it's very pretty.
OK, come on, teeth
and in pajamas.
- Oh no!
- Oh yes!
Come on, really.
I'm coming.
Funny music
Bring him back at 8 p.m.
But he has school tomorrow!
- I only have it on weekends!
- Keep going, and you'll get it again.
And that,
It's because I stuck something on
on my car door.
- If you hadn't smashed through the bush...
- Mom ?
I know what I want
for my birthday.
Let's all do it.
- WITH PLEASURE, MY LOVE.
- This evening,
Can I sleep with the light on?
I'm scared.
- Yes, of course, you can.
- It's your fault he's scared!
- For what ?
- Well... I don't know!
Did you see what you did to me?
in his bag?
A first aid kit, a blood pressure monitor...
- Yeah.
- And a venom extractor! Who makes those?
- All the mothers.
- But not to go to a park.
Intriguing music
She sighs.
Whose is this?
So, have you found someone?
Madam is not wasting any time.
- Are you going to stop?
- The lucky one?
A colleague from the animal shelter?
- Maybe it's the plumber
who has forgotten it.
- He's here, right? Where is he?
- T'es ridicule.
- If you don't want to tell me, no problem.
I'll find it myself.
the plumber.
Funny music
Are we serious here?
She laughed softly.
- It's a gift from my mother.
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
- Okay then,
Where is he?
He's lucky
that I didn't run into him.
When I see
that after such a short time,
You're capable of replacing me,
I tell myself that ultimately,
I haven't lost anything.
Hi, Tess.
He closes the door.
She sighs.
It starts.
Melancholic music
- KISSES, DAD!
- We love you so, so, so, so much.
- They love me.
Fear.
Joy.
Anger.
- Not happy!
Are you serious?
It went like clockwork.
- KISSES, DAD!
We love you...
fort, fort, fort, fort.
Let's go in.
He groaned.
Funny music
- Who is it, Mr. Ticoule?
- I don't know... Stéphane?
You do it to me every morning.
- Yes, that's true.
Next time, I'll change my voice.
- Yes.
- It's quite a construction site here.
- Yeah, I slept here.
I had a lot of work.
A coffee?
- Oh yes, with pleasure.
- Ticoule,
The boss wants to see you.
Ominous music
Sit down.
- You asked to see me, Mr. Malone?
A problem with the accounting balance sheet?
- It's in this park, Zoo'Nimaux,
de Jeffrey Malone,
suspected of having given
one of his competitors to his hyenas,
that a man would have penetrated
the zoo enclosure.
Probably drunk,
he would have unfortunately
caused a short circuit
responsible for the opening
animal grids.
Panic spread
in the village,
as these images show.
Fast Music
Coups de klaxon
Barrissement
Cris
This man is a testament to that
present in the park
who crossed paths with a hippopotamus.
The animal attacked?
- No, but I would have preferred that.
Hippos are very affectionate.
during their mating season.
- Right away,
the weather...
- You see,
This guy?
He had to do a job
In my opinion.
He sighs.
- I am very sorry.
I don't know how to make amends.
- I know.
You're going to replace him.
But he had to do
What kind of job?
- A cruise in South America.
- Uh, is there a catch?
And bring me back
A package. There are fewer checks.
by boat rather than by plane.
- There was a trap.
- You're leaving next week.
- Next week?
No, I can't.
Sorry.
Since it's the birthday
of my son, we promised
to do it together,
It's really complicated, you know.
- No problem.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Wait, wait!
No, I agree.
I agree, I agree.
Ominous music
- There is one rule:
Never open the package.
Are you going there with your wife?
and your son.
You'll be able to blend in more easily.
- No problem.
But let me out.
Ah, they're getting closer!
Anything you want!
I beg you!
Don't disappoint me.
- A cruise in South America.
- I have prices
with my CE.
I thought to myself... That's it.
- Is this a joke?
- No way.
Leo, would you be happy if we left?
On holiday for your birthday?
That would be great!
But if you promise
not to argue.
- I promise you.
I am ready to make the effort.
Not you, Tess?
- Yes!
Yes, that would be great.
That's a good idea.
- Super.
- Come on,
Go to the swing.
- You're going to pass
A very good holiday.
- Aren't you coming with us?
He sighs.
- You've come to play
With me?
- Yes, we're coming.
I'm not sleeping with you.
- I prefer the doormat,
It will sting less.
Slight growl
What is the main point?
Is it so that our son is happy?
Leo, create.
- Oh la la la la!
- It wasn't me! I'm innocent!
- Trafficker or victim?
This French national,
a good family man,
He has just been sentenced to 30 years.
detention
in a Mexican prison
for having transported a package
whose contents he claims to be unaware of.
Funny music
- Hop.
Groans of exertion
Mobile phone ringtone
Heavy breathing
- Hello ?
- Hello.
It's NRJ.
We're offering you two dream weeks
on a crossing
between South America and France
if you answer a question.
What is your favorite radio station?
- RTL.
- Uh... Are you sure?
It's NRJ
who calls you to ask you
What is your favorite radio station?
- I know myself, it's RTL.
I know what I'm talking about, though.
- Well, you're in luck,
because at NRJ too,
Our favorite radio station is RTL.
You win two dream weeks.
- Really ?
I'm lucky
that we have the same tastes.
We'll send you all the information.
on your phone. Hi!
Groan
Rhythmic Latin music
- Welcome to the international airport
from Palombia.
Thank you for joining us...
- Sir, please!
Could you take the red bag?
Excuse me.
THANKS.
I recognize you.
You sang in the band
To Be Dos, avec Juanito.
- It's possible.
- I don't dare ask you.
- Go for it,
I'm used to it.
- Oh yeah?
An autograph from Juanito
Please.
What an incredible solo career.
He's selling a bunch of records.
God...
What did I say?
- Stéphane?
- Mr. Ticoule?
- More...
- What a coincidence!
- What are you doing?
- A crazy story.
I won a CFC cruise
thanks to RTL.
Are you kidding me?
- Non.
- I'm going too.
- Is that true?
- Yes, indeed.
Are we sharing the same taxi?
- Yes, with pleasure.
I came with my family.
Tess, Leo!
Stéphane, with whom I work.
- Hello, nice to meet you.
- Delighted.
You're better in real life
than in a photograph.
- Where did you see me in a photo?
- At the office, on the doormat.
A little forced laugh
- I'm going to get a trolley, I'll be back.
- That's it.
A small, embarrassed laugh
- I just landed. Where do I go?
- I'm sending you the GPS coordinates.
At the gas station restrooms.
Your contact will be waiting for you there.
with the package.
He has a tattoo on his left hand.
- OK.
He laughed.
- Wait, wait.
What do you mean, I don't have a limousine?
OK. And how do I do that?
To go to the boat, me?
Rhythmic Latin music
- Can we stop at the gas station?
- Yes, sir.
- I'm going to pee
And I'll get something to drink.
Intriguing music
- I am allergic to mosquitoes.
I mustn't get bitten.
- It bothers me less than the fishing rod.
Why did you take it?
- Because we're going on a boat.
- It's a cruise ship.
- I took a long fishing rod.
"Spa".
You are a masseuse.
- No, it's SPA.
It's for the animals.
- Do you massage animals?
- Oh, hi! Hi!
Can we please take a photo?
Oh, thank you so much.
- OK.
- Yes, please.
- Here we go.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
With my husband.
- Yeah, yeah, of course. Yes.
- Yay!
- OK, thank you.
- Wait, wait, wait, please.
One more, one more photo.
With a friend.
Funny music
Your contact will be waiting for you there.
with the package.
He has a tattoo on his left hand.
- Hello.
Intriguing music
Good morning.
I am David.
- Money?
- Ah yes, of course.
Funny music
He sighs.
- No, but... smoking
at a gas station...
People
They are really stupid.
Tension music
Cris
Suppressed remarks
- Pardon? I didn't understand.
- "Donate the sack."
- The bag?
No, please, not the bag.
- He's going to blow everything up.
- Is anyone there?
- "Close the safe, come on!"
- Wait, we can work something out.
- "Posamente el saco par terro."
There you go. Thank you.
Groan
"Market, my pistolet!"
We have to go,
That's dangerous!
- "No, the sack!"
- Hurry up !
- Go for it.
- "I don't want the car!"
- Hold on tight!
He shouts.
- It's getting closer!
We're going to catch fire.
- Don't worry.
There's water!
A canard caquette.
Tension music
- It's stuck. It's stuck.
Quickly.
Come on, come on, open up!
- Come on.
- Quickly !
- I'm stuck!
He shouts.
- Come on, get out!
Pardon.
Sorry about your bag.
He's the only one
that I couldn't save.
- Nevermind.
No problem.
- Okay, so are you coming?
There are taxis there.
Latin Music
Intriguing music
Whirlwind Music
Discussion in English
- I have arrived.
- Raymond !
- Yes, the Renaissance.
- Okay, I'll leave you now.
- Raymond !
Did you have a good trip?
Hélène. Pleased to meet you.
I'm going to film you on the cruise
for season 3
Extreme Customs Officers.
Sorry, I'm a bit busy.
- It looks really heavy.
Gasping breath
- Pardon.
- Good morning.
- Excuse me.
Whoops, sorry, excuse me.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
You are ?
- It's good ?
Is that enough for you?
Come on.
Well, obviously,
They don't have a TV here.
Protestations
Yes, okay, it's fine, it's fine.
I was there. That was my place.
- Good morning.
- Hello. First name?
- Stéphane.
- Name.
Ah yes, my name is Stéphane.
What do you mean, "no"?
- Give me your passport.
You are about to go through security.
- Good morning.
Intriguing music
Beep
- Put down your bag. Thank you.
- Carlos! Carlos, come.
Can you follow me?
- Is there a problem?
- Random check.
We'll meet on board.
OK ?
- You put it in suite 216.
Yes ?
Ah, here's the star of the boat.
Nice to meet you, Helmut.
- Helmut ?
We just received your costume.
Funny music
Isn't it magnificent?
Coco, the head of entertainment.
I can't wait to see you on stage.
Whirlwind Music
- Welcome aboard the Renaissance,
a chic mix
and luxury. A crossing
between South America and France
for an exceptional cruise
who will leave you
Unforgettable memories.
Renaissance, a dream at sea.
Intriguing music
Heartbeats
Groan of effort
Funny music
- Sir ?
- Yes ?
- Did you climb all 7 floors on foot?
- Yes.
- You had an elevator
on the ground floor.
- Ah good ?
THANKS.
Well, I'm going back then.
- Uh...
Groans of panic
Heavy breathing
Sigh of relief
- Hein ?
- Ouch!
- You want to leave your country?
I'll help you.
Are you scared? Don't be scared.
You must be hungry.
Attends.
I have an idea.
Mmm!
It's good.
Mmh mmh. Come on, let's go.
Come on, go ahead.
Come out of your bag.
But come.
Hop.
They are coated peanuts.
of chocolate.
Mmm, it's very good.
Look at.
It's crunchy.
There's a knock.
Hide! Hide!
We don't have any soap.
in our bathroom.
Do you have any extra?
- Yes of course.
Please come back in.
There's a knock.
- Customs police.
Tension music
- I'm coming !
- YOU !
- "Son of Speculoos!"
- Chut!
- Don't tell me to shush!
- Yes, yes, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Funny music
Yes ?
- Stéphane Buisson?
- Yes, why?
- We have a big problem.
- Ah good ?
- No way!
Is it almost over?
Shock
- Sorry.
- Why give away your bag?
- I took the wrong bag at the airport.
I mistook his for mine.
They are both red.
By the way, your soap.
Ouch...
Tension music
- Ah, Raymond, I have good news.
- Oh!
Are you going to take a shower?
- Uh, no.
We have just received
the trailer for season 2.
Look.
Musique rock
We filmed for 100 days.
ordinary men
who do an extraordinary job.
We followed them
in their operations,
and also in their private lives.
- Surprise !
- Thank you, darling. Thank you very much.
Discover the daily lives of these men,
for whom is team spirit
is the most important.
- THANKS.
- You're welcome. Now get dressed.
- And where possible,
the seizures are redistributed
to the most destitute.
Cheers
- Look
what I brought back for you;
iPhone 15 cases!
That will make you some hats.
The big one,
I have something for you.
Yes, sneakers.
You may have made them.
And the icing on the cake,
Ski equipment!
And what's more, with the promo code
"extreme customs officer",
You will receive a 10% discount.
Here, get out of here.
Your T-shirt is disgusting.
You're going to wreck the car.
Goodbye, kind gentleman!
Thank you!
- EXTREME CUSTOMS OFFICERS!
- Well, the assembly is not final.
- I hope.
- For season 3,
More action is needed
and more sensationalism.
- Well, that's convenient.
There appears to be a trafficking of exotic animals.
on the boat.
- Oh yeah?
Tension music
- Give me this bag
or I'll punch your lights out.
- Oh yeah?
Go ahead, I'll be waiting for you.
- I wasn't expecting that answer.
Moans
- Hello, how are you?
Intriguing music
We open the door.
- What did you take?
- Nothing.
- Show me your hands.
Funny music
Show me your left hand.
Slight moan
Tension music
She moaned.
Action music
Wait for me!
- You wanted action?
Go ahead and film it.
It's going to be huge.
- OK.
He shouts.
Raymond ?
How are you ?
He groaned.
- Not great.
- Who was it?
The guy in your closet?
- A migrant hidden in my suitcase.
- That's not possible,
That's illegal, Stéphane.
You risk going to prison for that.
- I know. I was unconscious.
- I need you to keep
my son's gift
in your room.
- Did he do poorly at school?
- Stéphane,
However, it's a surprise.
Don't tell anyone.
I will give it to him in France.
OK ?
- OK.
- I'm going to put it right there, okay?
To no one, Stéphane.
Who do we talk to about this?
- Person.
- So.
Key beeps
There you go. Great.
Thank you, Stéphane. We...
What are blue pills?
What are you taking?
Is that what I'm thinking?
Are you waiting for someone?
- Hein? No, no, no.
It's the sun.
I should never have worn those shorts.
There was no more Biafine.
As a result,
The pharmacist told me:
"Take these blue pills."
"That way, the sheets will touch more
your thighs."
I didn't understand.
Funny music
- Of course.
She also gave me
red pills.
They are sleeping pills.
When I sleep with someone...
Goodbye, Stéphane.
- Sorry, I won't be able to keep you.
No, don't look at me like that.
Stop.
Okay, you won.
You can stay again tonight.
But tomorrow, you're off.
It'll be OK.
Oh! By the way,
I thought of something.
It's for your needs.
- Hein ?
Intriguing music
- Good news and bad news.
Where do I start?
- As you wish.
- I was able to board.
- What is the right one?
Latin Music
- Are you alright, darling?
Not too much sunburn?
It's already 7 p.m.
- I warned
that I would be in your room.
- Excuse me? What is this nonsense?
- Just like you said!
I'm already coming nicely
to sing on this boat.
I arrive here, they've forgotten
to reserve a room for me.
Thank you for the troubleshooting.
- Normal,
with what you've done for us
today, anyway.
- Yeah.
Intriguing music
Key beeps
Ringtone
Key beep
- What are you doing ?
- Hein ?
- Do you want some food?
- "I'm not mine."
- I have a small crust of bread, if you would like.
Blows
Heavy breathing
- Oh, no.
Blows
Vibrator
- Mr. Ticoule,
There's a small problem
with your son's gift.
- What's going on?
Soft music
Gazouillis
What is this?
- The treasure of Palombia.
The rarest animal in the world.
The Marsupilami.
Heavy breathing
It's a miracle.
He laughed.
For the Palombianos,
It's a legend.
For me, it's my whole life.
Buzzing
My mission is to protect him.
Now that I'm here,
Nothing can happen to you anymore.
Squeak
- I got it! I got it!
Ah yes, sorry.
- No, no, no, no!
"What idiots!"
We need to go into that room.
- So how do we do it?
I'm not a burglar.
- With your key, this is your room.
Look, there are your ex's things.
- Oh, no...
- He's not very bright, is he?
- Yeah.
Funny music
- Chut.
She moaned.
Squeak
They are shouting.
- Mom !
- Nothing broken?
- No, it's fine.
How are you?
- Yes, it's fine.
- Wait. Could you help us?
- Everything is fine ?
- You've come at a good time.
Will you help me lift the wardrobe?
- How are you ?
Come on, let's go.
Mechanism
David ?
Slight squeaks
- Dad?
- Why are you hiding?
- It's what
that moves
sous ton T-shirt ?
- Uh...
A small, embarrassed laugh
- Happy Birthday
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, LEO
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
- Go ahead,
Give him his gift.
- Hein ?
- Well, his gift.
- Ah.
- Well, go ahead.
- Happy birthday, my darling.
Soft music
Gazouillis
We shouldn't talk about it.
Animals are not allowed on the boat.
- But I wanted a console.
- You're offering it to him
A wild animal?
Are you sure he's not dangerous?
- No, but it's a baby, there's nothing to worry about.
- What species?
- Don't you recognize it?
- Oh no.
- Well yes, it is...
- Grandma!
- It's a...
- A cat.
A Palombian cat.
With a very long tail.
Here, they call it the long-tailed cat.
- Excuse me, who are you?
- He climbed in illegally.
But it's not dangerous.
The poor man wants to flee his country.
"That's not the truth."
- No, listen. Me,
I won't say anything about the cat.
But please,
Let me keep it too.
We're going to go wash up.
- "Que toilette?"
"Lachamete, please!"
- We're going to put some foam on it.
- Foam?
- I wanted a console.
- Grandma!
Latin Music
- And he likes that?
- He likes all fruits.
To have an animal kidnapped
just to give as a gift...
Is your son doing well?
Carefree ?
- Why are you on this boat?
What is the truth, huh?
- I'm here to make up for my mistakes.
I was the only one who knew
where its nest was located,
thanks to a card
that I designed myself.
It was stolen from me
pair of bandits!
His place is in the jungle.
not in an apartment.
- An apartment?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, of course, you're right.
That's a bad idea.
But perhaps you could help me
to retrieve it. Since it's me
who gave it to my son,
It's a delicate matter.
I don't want to hurt her feelings.
I am his father.
- OK.
As soon as we approach the coast,
I'll go to your room to get it.
You tell him that he escaped...
A mythomaniac.
You are a specialist.
- Yes, great. Let's do that.
- But how do we transport it?
He is likely to be very agitated.
- There's no problem.
Stéphane Buisson.
He has sleeping pills.
- Bingo !
- Yes !
If this animal is so important to you,
Why not call the police?
- It is extremely sought after.
That would put him in danger.
"Capichos?"
From now on,
No one should know anymore
of his presence here.
Person.
Hello!
I made a new friend.
He's so cute.
Don't hesitate to like the video
if you find it cute.
Or share.
Are you ready, Bibi?
- Bibi !
- Oh, pardon !
Calm music
Remarks in a foreign language
-Bibi !
- OH !
Remarks in a foreign language
- It's the buzz of the moment!
For his wife's birthday,
A Saudi is ready to pay you
one million dollars
if you bring the animal back to him.
I don't know what you're going to do,
But I'm going hunting.
- How much did the guy from the zoo pay us?
- 10 000.
- OK, let's go back.
Dark music
Brouhaha
- Okay, I've taken...
- You're crazy!
Leo is afraid of everything
And you're giving him a monkey?
Is this a joke?
It's anything but a feline.
Couldn't you have taken an orangutan?
- He already has your mother.
And if you're not happy,
Go away with your new boyfriend.
- I don't have a new boyfriend.
Don't take me for a fool.
I saw it,
the guy hiding in the closet.
I didn't fight with him
Because Leo was there.
- The guy hiding in my closet?
And you couldn't have said that?
We were burgled.
I'm dreaming, you caught the burglar
For my boyfriend?
It was a bad idea
to leave together.
- I completely agree.
- Like Leo's gift.
Couldn't you have taken a book?
- He looked very happy.
- No, he wasn't.
He wanted a game console.
- I wanted to do something original...
- Grandma!
Nostalgic music
Gazouillis
- Leave me alone, I want to be by myself.
Leave me alone, I'm telling you!
Squeak
He shouts.
Horrified scream
Funny music
Don't move.
Gazouillis
No, stop!
- What's going on?
- He's drinking the shower gel!
- Wow !
- Descends !
Are you serious?
- I didn't do it on purpose.
Wow wow wow wow.
Music in slow motion
Funny music
- It's too high.
I can't catch it.
- You can take the step stool.
He laughed.
- But I can't,
Come help me.
- Yes of course.
- I'm coming.
Gazouillis
- Okay, I've got it!
Tess and Leo laugh.
It was toilet water.
- Oh, that makes you laugh?
Leo laughs.
And that makes you laugh?
And that makes you laugh? So?
What are you going to do with that?
"Mr. Blue Sky"
Electric Light Orchestra
Ah, you want war?
Do you want war?
Gazouillis
It wasn't me!
- Oh yeah?
- It's not my fault!
- It's not my fault either.
Leo, on Dad!
Burp then wonder
He laughed.
Are you crazy or what?
It wasn't me, it was him.
- To bed.
- The first one to laugh
gets a slap.
Got it? Let's go.
It's grunting.
He laughed.
You laughed, you lost.
- Grandma!
Are you sick or something?
Majestic music
- Saute! Saute! Saute!
- Come on, come on!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah !
- Here we go !
- No, but come on, shoot!
He laughed.
Encourage mom!
"Mr. Blue Sky"
Electric Light Orchestra
- Yeah! Yeah!
Musique hip-hop
- Grandma!
Leo laughs.
He laughed.
Grandma!
Fracas
- Who was it?
- I don't know.
It's okay. Shall we go back?
Truth or dare?
- ACTION !
They laugh.
Soft music
Intriguing music
- Raymond, are you feeling better?
- Yes. I'm moving around more and more.
my feet.
- Ah, formidable.
Raymond ?
Raymond, right here.
I discovered something
that I had never seen before.
- Deodorant?
- No. Him.
- It's our exotic pet.
- With him, we can create a buzz.
- If the child is found,
The animal is found.
- Do you know what this is?
This is my favorite manga:
Dragon Ball.
And that's Goku.
When he's angry, that's when he has
Long yellow hair, like yours.
When he wants to fight,
a large fireball
it comes out of his hands, just like that.
I've already tried, but it doesn't work.
And these are the 7 crystal balls.
When you put them together,
A large dragon appears.
And you can make any wish.
Soft music
I already know which one I would do.
We open the door.
Gazouillis
- What's my man doing?
More manga...
There's a knock.
Cache Bibi
and join your mother for breakfast.
Hide Bibi. Go ahead, hide him.
- Wait for me here, I'll be back soon.
So.
- Ah, hello, Stéphane.
- It's for Leo's birthday.
- It's true ?
- Yes.
- You shouldn't have.
Funny music
But Leo is 6 years old, right?
- It's from 6 months old.
- See you later, Dad.
- See you later.
- Well, aren't you going to give it to him?
Intriguing music
Gazouillis
- He!
He burps.
What are you doing ?
Don't drink that!
Non !
Come on, stop, I told you!
Get down from there.
Funny music
Don't move.
Don't move!
Ringtone
- Guess who it is, Mr. Malone.
- Ticoule !
- Oh no,
missed.
This is Stéphane Buisson.
- Bush ?
What are you doing here?
Did you open the package?
- What are you talking about?
Don't take me for a fool!
- What's going on?
- I'm talking about what you brought back
illegally.
The little thing with the big eyes,
a large truffle
and who strikes with his tail.
- Ah good ?
- Be careful.
Even though he looks very cute,
It can be very dangerous.
- What do you want me to do?
- Knock him out, if you have to!
He sighs.
- We are finalizing the experiments
about the lynx.
Everything is going perfectly.
- We have to do something!
It's unmanageable.
That's nonsense!
- Calma!
- He's turning the whole room upside down!
There is a solution.
- It's what ?
- A piranha.
- He eats piranhas?
- That calms him down.
- Super !
And where are we going to find a piraña?
- I saw loads of them in the aquarium.
- How do you fish for it?
I don't even have a fishing rod.
Funny music
And there was only him
To catch a piranha?
He wouldn't lend it to me.
his fishing rod.
Why did he put me
A guitar riff?
"Son of a bald man!"
- Do you know its value?
The one from my 2004 tour.
- Keep yourself busy
of your weight problems.
He laughed.
- I haven't gained a single gram in 20 years.
I have back problems.
- There are too many people,
We'll never succeed.
We're going to get roasted.
- We need to create a diversion.
I think I have an idea.
- I'm not going up there.
- Where are you planning to sleep?
Babillage
- Are you okay, my love?
There, he is well protected
of the nasty sun.
It's good.
- I request your attention.
Come closer to discover
our flyboard demonstration.
Using its remote control,
our professional
will launch into the air
Ricky Salsa
thanks to reactors at its feet.
Let's applaud!
There you go!
Epic music
He laughed.
Tension music
- Where is the baby?
The baby laughs.
He's here!
He's not here.
He's here. He's not here.
Cri
He's not here.
- He!
Groan of effort
I swear to you, darling,
I don't understand what happened.
I was playing as usual.
I said, "He's here,
"He's not here"...
He laughed.
Well, he's back.
Moans
- Oh, I'm sorry!
Do something!
He's eating me alive!
- I'll fix that!
He shouts.
Groan of effort
Dark music
Moans
Help me!
- There you go, that's good, you'll be able to
Give me a sound test.
He shouts.
Squeaking
We can now resume the report.
- On what?
- The Customs Officers of the Extreme.
- Ah. If you want to do
a slightly larger audience,
Film me, I don't mind.
They laugh.
- No, that's kind of you.
We don't have time.
We need to find a yellow monkey.
- With black spots?
Intriguing music
If I tell you who owns this monkey,
Would you like to do a report?
On my next album?
Vibrator
- Are you feeling better, my Bibi?
Hey, look, I have some fresh fish.
- Hello ?
- There, Ticules ?
- Yes.
- Now is the time.
I'm picking up the marsupilami tonight.
And I'm taking him back to Palombia.
OK ?
Sad music
- OK for me.
- Wait. That, Bibi, you see,
This is my favorite photo.
That was when my dad and mom,
They were still in love.
Just before Dad does it again
A huge mistake.
Mobile phone ringtone
Light music
- Yes, my darling?
- Hi, darling.
Reassure me,
Did you remember Leo's show?
- Of course.
Come on, champion.
Otherwise your mother will kill me.
Come on, let's go.
Super.
How are you ?
Did the show go well?
I am very sorry
for not having come.
I suggest we don't tell Mom.
This stays between us.
I think she's calling me.
Hello ?
- Did you get it back?
- Yes, I got it back, of course.
He's right in front of... me.
You know what? I'll call you back.
Why didn't you tell me anything?
But... what?
- Amber Alert.
A child has been abducted.
Amber Alert
from the Ministry of Justice.
- Since Dad hadn't come,
I walked home, I got lost.
A gentleman kindly offered
to bring me back.
- It's always been like that,
his problem with Martine.
You give him your arm,
It's eating your calf.
Let her go
with his Jean-Luc!
He's his colleague.
Haven't you had a bit too much to drink?
to drive,
Sir ?
- You're right, kid.
We're going to take the subway.
That's safer.
-Subway or car?
This driver hesitated before making his choice...
both.
He quickly designated
a certain Jean-Luc
as the person responsible for the accident.
- My mother never forgave him.
She says he only thinks about himself.
You don't know your parents.
Bibi, but don't worry,
I am here.
Melancholic music
Dad, do you think that one day
We can take Bibi
within his family?
- Uh... Yes, of course.
- Do you promise me?
- I promise you, yes.
- Bibi, I'm going to eat.
But don't worry, I'll be back soon.
Tension music
Song in Spanish
- Your turn!
Losses, losses, losses
- A little bit of gel.
- That makes 5 times today.
I'm not made of sugar.
- That's what I was telling your mother
when I was there.
- But since you were never there.
- If you had wanted to, you wouldn't have refused
my marriage proposal.
- That's irrelevant. My name is Tess,
Your name is Ticoule.
- Well?
- T'imagines
The priest's head?
Latin Music
- I'll be right back.
You can go into the room.
Did you take the sleeping pill?
- Yeah.
- Super.
- Ticoule,
I was wrong about you.
You're a great guy.
Really.
- No, don't believe that.
- Ah good ?
- I'm not there enough for my family.
- Watch out for that, Ticoule.
My father abandoned us
overnight.
He won the lottery and bought himself a plane.
a house in France, a motorcycle,
lots of HDMI cables...
I don't know why.
My mother raised us all alone.
by the strength of her rolls of fat.
- Was that a long time ago?
- Last year.
- Helmut! Are you making fun of me?
I'm looking for you.
- For what ?
- Are you serious? It's going to be your turn.
Come on, come on, come on! This is your moment.
Did you rehearse the choreography properly?
- Hold.
Have a good sleep.
And I'll take you home.
He laughed.
There's a knock.
Intriguing music
Groan
Raymond crie.
Pablito groaned.
- So, where is he, Ticoule?
- Ticoule ?
- Where is the creature?
- Wait. I'm sorry.
My camera battery died.
- Ah good ?
What should we do?
- Well, it would have to be redone.
- Ah.
- Sorry.
- Good.
- "What pastime?"
- Nothing. You don't change a thing, you're perfect.
You're not moving, are you?
It's good ?
Did you change it?
- And action!
Raymond crie.
Pablito groaned.
- Where is he, Ticoule?
Where is the little creature?
- "What beast?"
- Okay, did you get it?
- Top. Canon.
- Well, you know what?
Turn off the camera.
You're going to make me
a photo
for my personal collection.
- "Castagnettas."
- You came on the wrong day.
He laughed.
Bibi rit.
- Grandma!
He shouts.
Tension music
You're here, aren't you...?
Moans
Cheers
- Now, you're all waiting for it.
And some came from all over the world
to see it.
On clappe, on clappe pour Falky !
- Yeah !
- Allez, on clappe
Even the Scots!
- Falky, he's your friend
- FALKY ! FALKY !
FALKY ! FALKY !
Rhythmic music
Children's cries
FALKY ! FALKY !
Tension music
Cris
- Bloody hell!
He shouts.
Bagpipe music
Action music
- Auntie! Auntie!
Groan of effort
Moans
- Ticoule !
Children's cries
Raymond crie.
- Raymond !
- Oh, calm down!
- I messed everything up!
Can you do it again?
- Cleared !
- It stings the eyes,
But it's not a big deal.
- "Stop! Stop, Bibi!"
"Stop!"
THANKS.
- And the sleeping pill?
- I gave it to him!
I gave him some
two !
Two sleeping pills!
- That's not a sleeping pill.
- It's what,
If they're not sleeping pills?
- It's not for the same reason.
- Hein ?
- Grandma!
Why is he knocked out?
He stutters.
- I saw him being dragged by a customs officer.
- What's wrong with her tail?
- Hey, you!
Give me that animal!
Give me that animal,
right away !
- Give him this animal,
right away.
Classical music
- No, I don't think so.
"The Blue danube"
Johann Baptist Strauss
Moans
- Let go of me!
- So.
How are you ?
Is the wax too hot?
- Non.
Barking
They are screaming.
Moans
She screams.
Barking
Moans
- Mom ?
- How are you.
- Sorry, darling!
Excuse me. Are you alright, head-wise?
I didn't do it on purpose.
We're going to add some ice cubes.
Tension music
He sniffs.
Intriguing music
- Hello?
- Yes, customs police speaking.
I have some questions
on one of your employees.
David Ticoule.
- I'm listening to you.
He is involved
in an animal trafficking operation.
- There is a way to work things out
between people of goodwill.
- But it's called
That's corruption, sir.
Don't take it like that.
- That interests me, go ahead.
- Listen to me.
- Yes?
Bring me back the animal,
Arrest David Ticoule.
- Very well. And what?
Come see me at the zoo
And I will know how to be generous.
- Generous?
Generous in what way?
Gasping breath
- We did it!
We did it!
The elevator will go down.
Laughing contentedly
Tope is!
Sad music
- Give me the marsupilami.
Are you serious?
I have no choice.
I absolutely must bring him back
In France.
Don't force me to be violent.
- I should have thought of that.
Trusting a man
who betrays his family...
Elevator beep
Tension music
Let's go.
Come on, come on.
Moans
- Where are we?
- Chut!
Keep quiet.
We were stormed
by pirates.
- Ah good ?
- Yes.
- I'm soaked.
- You were stung by a jellyfish.
- So what?
You can thank me.
If it doesn't burn you. Mmh?
- Hein ?
Oh, Captain!
Captain!
Are you aware of this?
There's a hostage situation.
- Well, obviously!
- What are you going to do?
- You remain hidden.
I will apply
the appropriate protocol.
- But what is the protocol?
Tension music
- Here, the port of Étretat.
Answer.
Change course.
You are approaching the coast.
Moans
- "Dousamente!"
- Sit down.
- I'm going to try something.
Hey !
Hey ! Hey !
Listen.
You leave the boat,
and I'm offering you tickets
for my concert
in Jouy-en-Josas.
- Never mind, I'll take care of it.
Come on, let's go.
Ricky Salsa.
How convenient to meet again.
- Do we know each other?
- The number of letters
that I was able to send you back then!
And never a reply.
- Sorry, but I was receiving them...
- Sing!
- Pardon ?
- You will sing and dance for me.
- Like some kind of private concert?
- Yeah, that's it.
Seductive music
- OK.
Song in Spanish
Zipper
Ominous music
- We are looking for an animal,
YELLOW,
with black spots.
We know he is on that boat.
Groan
The passengers will be thrown out
overboard...
Groans of panic
until we get it.
- What's going on?
- I can feel his tail in my sleeve.
I think he's dreaming.
- If anyone has any information about this animal,
that he raises his hand.
Moans
You,
Do you know where he is?
- Non.
- You raise your hand.
- To tell you that I,
I don't know where he is.
- Approach.
- Why me?
- Come here.
Ominous music
Heavy breathing
Do you know where he is or not?
Moans
Heavy breathing
- You're welcome.
- HIM!
- It wasn't me.
It wasn't me. It wasn't...
A small, embarrassed laugh
How are you ?
Are you having a good time?
Because...
He sobs.
It wasn't me.
Moans
- You want to show off?
Bring the kid back to me.
- Don't touch him.
- LEAVE HIM ALONE!
Moans
- Either you tell me where he is,
Either I throw the kid in the water.
What is this now?
- I'm warning you,
YOU,
if you touch a single hair...
He groaned.
Oh, sorry, little one!
- That's enough, he won't talk.
Kill him.
Tragic music
- Go ahead, shoot.
I don't care.
I will never betray him.
In any case, gentlemen,
I hid it so well
that you will never find him again.
Never.
- Grandma!
- There it is, my million dollars.
- Don't touch Bibi!
- Move.
Leave him alone!
- You didn't understand
what I just told you.
Tension music
Groans of exertion
- Smash them, Bibi.
- Catch the animal.
Rock music
Screams of struggle and moans
The Marsupilami laughed.
He groaned.
Now it's just the two of us.
Tension music
A little laugh
Rhythmic music
- Yeah, Bibi !
- Grandma!
Soft music
- My card...
My card.
- Bibi, you're the strongest.
Muffled voice
What's going on?
Is everything alright?
Sad music
He groaned.
- No, no!
- You're crazy!
Why did you do that?
- This animal has no business being here.
He saved us
the life !
- If he hadn't been there,
The pirates wouldn't have come.
- What are you going to do with him?
- This beast attacked me.
It needs to be injected.
- What ?
- Non !
- Stop!
It might sting you too.
- You don't have the right!
- I am a customs officer.
- Non !
You don't have the right!
- Wait.
The deal is cancelled.
You never told me you wanted to kill him.
- Start by saving your career.
Blame the trafficker
who made him go up
illegally on this boat
to deliver it to a zoo.
- Which trafficker?
- This trafficker. Bring him in.
- Dad?
- David ?
- Sorry, I had no choice.
- It's my birthday present!
Tell him, Dad.
Dad!
- Take him on board.
- Tess, believe me!
It's not my fault!
Leo, I'm sorry.
I'll explain it to you, I promise.
- One.
I can't believe it
that he lied to us.
It was him, the dolphin.
The music stops abruptly.
Tension music
Cris
Gasping breath
- He's here!
Don't move!
Non !
Theme from the film "The Big Blue"
Moans
Funny music
- Ticoule, wait!
Intriguing music
Heavy breathing
They're going to sting the marsupial.
Because of you!
I will never forgive you!
- If I didn't take it back to my boss...
He threw me to the hyenas.
And now I've lost everything.
My son, my family.
Stop whining!
Now, follow me.
We're going to save the marsupilami.
- And how?
- The customs officer.
We need to follow his every move.
If we find him,
We can still save Bibi.
Jingle
The search continues
to find
Pablito Camaron and David Ticoule.
The latter,
known to the police,
had kidnapped a deaf-mute child
at the school gate.
Right away, the economic point.
Intriguing music
- So.
- Your zoo,
What is it you're using as a cover?
- That's pretty much it.
Thanks to our experiences
about the animals in the zoo,
we are developing
pills capable of transmitting
the virtues of the different species.
For example, pills based on
of elephant DNA,
for the record.
The lynx, for its eyesight.
The Sloth, for children
hyperactive.
- Amazing.
- Yes.
- You wouldn't happen to have any pony DNA, would you?
Compared to the mane,
to the hair.
- Hmm.
- Okay, so what are you going to do with it?
of the marsupilami?
- For problems related to physical strength,
particularly due to age.
Okay, I'll walk you back.
It's a pleasure doing business with you.
- Shared pleasure.
You pay better than for TV.
Don't miss season 2!
Extreme Customs Officers.
Spy music
- "Dousamente."
"Dousamente."
- Yes yes.
Ringtone
- Ah, there he is.
Intriguing music
The music intensifies.
Tension music
Raymond crie.
Moans
Funny music in slow motion
Slow-motion moans
- Ticoule, not a move!
Tension music
- Drop your weapon!
Moans
Alright, let's get out of here!
- Come quickly!
Thank you for your help.
Ricky.
- That's normal.
If I thought less about my career,
We wouldn't be in this situation.
It's time to turn the page.
Juanito is better than me.
He has everything going for him.
- He is in bad shape.
He needs to be taken back to Palombia.
- So how do we do it?
Shall we walk there?
- I think I have a solution.
My father.
Musique hip-hop
Mobile phone ringtone
- Ah.
Look, a ghost from the past.
What do I deserve this honor?
- I need a service.
- Even though you didn't even come
At my wedding?
- Your wedding?
You let us down,
Mom and me!
You won the lottery
and have your midlife crisis.
- What crisis?
What crisis?
Who told you this nonsense?
If I left your mother,
It's for his own good.
Money has nothing to do with it.
OK, I accept
but on one condition:
that you finally accept
to meet your mother-in-law.
Hey, I'm switching to video.
- No, no, no.
- Hello to your wonderful son.
- Welcome, Pablito!
Welcome!
- And his sisters too.
- WOUHOU, PABLITO!
PABLITO! PABLITO!
PABLITO!
He laughed.
PABLITO! PABLITO!
- Pablito! Pablito!
- PABLITO! PABLITO!
- It's not the same, is it?
- It was nice of you to stop by,
But you can go.
- Oh no.
I want to cheer you up.
Moreover, you have
a very pretty tattoo
on the leg.
- It's a varicose vein.
- It's very well done.
There's a knock.
- David ?
- Dad?
- What are you doing here?
- I wanted to
so that you can say goodbye to him.
- Grandma!
Moving music
- It's you
Who saved him?
- With my new friends.
Tension music
Sirens
- What is this?
- There are cops everywhere.
Mobile phone ringtone
David, don't do anything stupid.
It's not too late.
I can still get you out
of this situation.
I came to an agreement with Raymond
so that you don't go to prison
and that you return to a normal life.
David, you have a choice:
return the beast to me
and get your old life back,
or refuse and go to prison.
far from your family.
Don't make a mistake this time.
- OK, I've made my choice.
This time,
I will make the right decision.
- I don't want them to take Bibi back.
- I promised you we'd bring him back
in his family.
The music intensifies.
That's what we're going to do.
Action music
- Police, stop!
- Stop!
- Oh, stop !
- Oh !
- They leave with the animal.
Take the wheel.
Funny music in slow motion
- Come on, let's head to the airfield.
Action music
Thumbtack.
- We need your car.
- No, no, no, no!
- Hold on tight!
- Come with me.
Pablito cried.
- Shoot out the tires.
Funny music in slow motion
- "Dousamente!"
"Calm down!"
Action music
- It's too late,
jerk !
And tuck your head in, there's a barrier
In the distance!
Funny music in slow motion
- Can you have the sugar?
- Yes, well, I'm busy!
Tire squeal
- Jean-Pierre!
Jean-Pierre!
- Red light. It's dangerous.
- We're not made of sugar.
Hang on.
They are shouting.
- They're here, Mom!
Catch them!
- Nicole ! Nicole !
He shouts.
Majestic music
He groaned.
They are shouting.
"The Birdcage"
Pierre Perret
- Open, open the birdcage
Watch them fly away, it's beautiful.
Children, if you can see...
He shouts.
Tire squeal
Action music
Groans of exertion
- Give it back to me!
- We'll meet at the airfield.
- Ticoule !
Ticoule !
Funny music in slow motion
- Stop!
He shouts.
Not a single move...
- Ticoule !
Stop!
Action music
Music in slow motion
Moans
Bip strident
"What's Up?"
4 Non Blondes
Gasping breath
It's over, Ticoule.
You made the wrong choice again.
David rit.
Can someone at least
Turn off the air conditioning?
- We did it, Bibi!
- Grandma!
- And there you have it!
- Can someone call...
- You're thinking of me
For Juanito's video?
- Yeah, I promise.
- THANKS.
- And David?
- My father will not come.
- Wait.
Who is it ?
Rock music
- That's my father.
- Shit.
- Dad.
- Son.
- Father!
Dad!
I missed you!
He sobs.
- Can you tell me
Where is the altimeter?
- Put on your glasses, Dad!
Stop acting like a young person.
- Don't do that again.
I can see perfectly well.
Here we go.
Moans
- Dad, are you okay?
"What's Up?"
4 Non Blondes
- Don't leave me here, oh!
Please don't leave me here!
I'm stuck.
What are you doing?
- But where is he, Dad?
- He won't be coming with us.
- For what ?
- Because he loves us very much.
Gazouillis
- By trying to be clever,
You'll end up like the animals in the zoo:
behind bars.
But what is this?
He shouts.
Happy laughter
What are you doing there?
- We have a few questions.
The journalist from Customs Officers called
about corruption
and animal abuse.
Soft music
- Stéphane,
I apologize for having taken you on this journey.
in all of this.
And thank you also for your help.
You are a beautiful person.
- Thank you, that really touches me.
Your apologies.
But deep down,
You're not the one truly responsible.
This is RTL.
- 300.
"Stopped."
Intriguing music
It's there.
Majestic music
Mushroom mushroom!
Grandma,
tes parents.
Soft music
Gazouillis
- I'm going to miss you, Bibi.
Life is really better
when you're there.
I will forget you
Never.
I love you.
The music intensifies.
Soft music
- Come on, you too.
Go back to your family.
Come on.
- Oh !
- I'm going to miss you.
A little laugh
Mobile phone ringtone
- Hello ?
- Salut, c'est Juanito.
Listen, even if my solo career
is at the top,
that I am the sex symbol
of an entire generation,
I would like to do
My next music video will be with you.
You deserve to return to the spotlight.
- Listen, we...
Yeah, we're talking about it, yeah.
- As long as this map exists,
The marsupilami will always be in danger.
- So we have to tear it up.
Majestic music
- If we do that,
That means we won't see him again.
Soft music
The music becomes majestic.
- Grandma!
A little laugh
Song in Spanish
Soft music
Melancholic music